Behind the world you know is a darkness you never imagined.
Mirrors 2 is a horror, mystery, fantasy film directed by Víctor García.
When Max, who is recovering from a traumatic accident, takes a job as a nighttime security
guard, he begins to see visions of a young mysterious woman in the store's mirror.
Max Matheson, played by Nick Stahl.
Jack Matheson, played by William Katt.
Elizabeth Reigns, played by Emmanuelle Vaugier.
Keller Landreaux, played by Lawrence Turner.
Jenna McCarty, played by Christy Carlson Romano.
Henry Schow, played by Evan Jones.
Mirrors is a 2008 American supernatural horror film directed by Alexandre
Aja, starring Kiefer Sutherland, Paula Patton, and Amy Smart.
The film was first titled Into the Mirror, but the
name was later changed to Mirrors.
Filming began on May 1, 2007, and it was released in
American theaters on August 15, 2008.
The film was originally scripted as a straightforward remake of
the 2003 South Korean horror film Into the Mirror.
However, once Aja was brought on board and read the script, he was
dissatisfied with the particulars of the original film's story.
He decided to retain the original film's basic idea involving mirrors, and to incorporate a few of
its scenes, but otherwise crafted a new story and script for his version of the movie.
A stand-alone sequel not featuring the original cast and
crew, titled Mirrors 2, was released in 2010.
The film explores themes of affectation, death,
aggressive, cautionary, admiring.
The tone is dark and mind_bending.